[Music]
I would say three or four things first
of all you know we asked the right
question to start with and we asked
bharga really what do you want to
achieve out of this and I think I still
remember his words he was very clear see
I want a very smooth time-bound
regulatory transparent and beneficial to
all uh deal to happen and that's what I
expect from the post merger integration
so I think when the leadership is very
clear from both sides and what they're
going to run after what they want to
achieve I think that was one great sort
of a stepping stone I think secondly I
think we drew up a joint scorecard and I
think that was pretty good for us that
our joint our scorecards were the same
absolutely the same what for these
scorecards this was all about whether we
can get the synergistic value whether we
can take cost out can we get additional
Revenue how do we settle the people in
how do we look at a new joint business
we actually had a unique team we had a
bunch of Industry Specialists we had
practitioners and then from our
Consulting business in ey and then we
have ey Parthenon we which specializes
in postmodger integration so we got a
postmodger integration office as a layer
on top to govern the entire project and
that governance was not only for ey it
was governing a joint team from icsa
Lombard and ey so that was one joint
team then looking at technology
looking at all the regulatory approvals
what are the approvals we will need at
what PowerPoint will they come if there
is a delay will we stop our work or what
will we do how will we deal with that
delay and if there's a delay what's the
catch-up mechanism
so and then you know you have various
streams how do they integrate to get the
value out uh that is there I I would say
technology was a very very big part I
think people might undermine that but
when you're doing such a big merger
imagine just you know merging a general
ledger the amount of thinking we have to
do how do we bring it together
[Music]